// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "According to the passage, indiscipline is seen as ",
    answer: "mondernity",
    options: [
      "mondernity",
      "development",
      "influence",
      "determination"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "One of the major things that determine the development of a country is ______",
    answer: "technology",
    options: [
      "society",
      "indiscipline",
      "phenomena",
      "technology"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The acts of indiscipline start from",
    answer: "home",
    options: [
      "modernity",
      "technology",
      "home",
      "society"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Indiscipline among youths does NOT result in",
    answer: "integrity",
    options: [
      "drug abuse",
      "secret cults",
      "rebellion",
      "integrity"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The major influuence in one's life is ______ responsibility",
    answer: "parental",
    options: [
      "parental",
      "technology",
      "societal",
      "environmental"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "According to the passage, a myth is also a",
    answer: "story",
    options: [
      "play",
      "story",
      "game",
      "drama"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "From the passage, we can infer that",
    answer: "every human community has myths",
    options: [
      "every human community has myths",
      "groups have myths",
      "africians do not have myths",
      "No one has myths"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The writer's opinion that myths are tied to _____ and _____ beliefs",
    answer: "cultural and social",
    options: [
      "education and reglious",
      "cultural and social",
      "occupation and marital",
      "religious and cultural"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "A title suitable for the passage is",
    answer: "myths",
    options: [
      "african myths",
      "myths",
      "non-afircan myths",
      "traditional myths"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Myths that relate to creation and supernatural powers are ______ myths",
    answer: "painting",
    options: [
      "ceramics design",
      "painting",
      "textile design",
      "graphic design"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Scinece and technology have assited the world in many ways through wonderful _________",
    answer: "inventions",
    options: [
      "inventions",
      "interventions",
      "intentation",
      "creations"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Virtually every nook and cranny of the world has felt the _______ of science and technology.",
    answer: "impart",
    options: [
      "impart",
      "feelings",
      "impacts",
      "actions"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "In the hospital, the ______ thermomater can be",
    answer: "clinical",
    options: [
      "medical",
      "mercury",
      "technical",
      "clinical"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "used to mesure the ______ of the body",
    answer: "temperature",
    options: [
      "temperature",
      "warmth",
      "coldness",
      "hotness"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Doctors use a ______ to listen to the heart beats",
    answer: "stethoscope",
    options: [
      "testhoscope",
      "strecthoscope",
      "stethoscope",
      "microscope"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "My mother and my sister _____ travelling to Kano next week",
    answer: "are",
    options: [
      "is",
      "was",
      "are",
      "am"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "When you _____ will you please help me?",
    answer: "finish",
    options: [
      "finishes",
      "had finished",
      "finish",
      "are finished"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "The train will leave ___ six o'clock exactly",
    answer: "at",
    options: [
      "on",
      "at",
      "by",
      "in"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Jane will continue to get low marks _____ she works harder",
    answer: "unless",
    options: [
      "however",
      "although",
      "unless",
      "even"
    ]
  },



  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "You will be in school tomorrow ____ you?",
    answer: "won't you",
    options: [
      "won't you",
      "will",
      "would",
      "don't"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "My father has bought a",
    answer: "brand new red car",
    options: [
      "brand red new car",
      "brand new red car",
      "red new brand car",
      "new brand red car"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "______ my father came to our school he has not talked to me",
    answer: "after",
    options: [
      "since",
      "but",
      "after",
      "although"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 23,
    question: "Neither the boys ____ the girls could answer the question",
    answer: "nor",
    options: [
      "or",
      "and",
      "nor",
      "both"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 24,
    question: "Tom climbed the stairs and ____ to bed",
    answer: "went",
    options: [
      "go",
      "went",
      "going",
      "goes"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "The counsellor warned the students to _____ from such behaviour in the future",
    answer: "desist",
    options: [
      "resist",
      "retreat",
      "desist",
      "denounce"
    ]
  },
];